hiliq.com 2019-09-16

# Privacy Policy - Wholesale Pure Nicotine , Best Nicotine Salt for sale, Cheap nicotine base, Buy E liquid nicotine wholesale

HiLIQ is committed to protecting your privacy. The following privacy policy applies to HiLIQ website and governs data collection and usage only at HiLIQ site and services.

1\. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION As an E-commerce website, HiLIQ collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by HiLIQ is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. HiLIQ does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.

2\. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION HiLIQ and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested. It is possible that HiLIQ may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from DWS and its affiliates. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. HiLIQ does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. HiLIQ does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. We may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served by HiLIQ or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of HiLIQ, including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of HiLIQ or the public.

3\. CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION HiLIQ offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences by emailing support@hiliq.com. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records. You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from HiLIQ by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.

4\. SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION HiLIQ is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through 128 bit encryption through GoDaddy SSL.

5\. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT HiLIQ will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how HiLIQ will use your personal information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. HiLIQ encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

6\. HILIQ WEBSITE UPDATE: TERMS AND CONDITIONS As part of HiLIQ terms and conditions for using the website, we can inform our customers when needed by message, email or newsletters about their tracking order number, new products and new promotions. By using our website to place an order means that you already accept those terms and conditions. In case you do not want to receive our newsletter or promotions service please feel free to contact us anytime to request the termination of the service and give us some basic information in order for us to verify your identity like: email, phone number and address. Once HiLIQ receive your request we will proceed with the termination. Please note that you can also unsubscribe from our newsletter directly by following few steps at the bottom page of the mail you received from us.you can unsubscriber from our newsletter directly by the unsusbcribe link insdide the newsletter

HiLIQ Co.,Limited  
Address: 2995 LiYue Road MinHang District Shanghai, China  
Phone: 1-888-568-6063  
Homepage: www.hiliq.com  
Email: service@hiliq.com
